Loneliness is much better when you have got someone to share it with.
The Station Agent is a drama, comedy film directed by Tom McCarthy.
When his only friend dies, a man born with dwarfism moves to rural New Jersey to live a life of
solitude, only to meet a chatty hot dog vendor and a woman dealing with her own personal loss.
Finbar McBride, played by Peter Dinklage.
Olivia Harris, played by Patricia Clarkson.
Joe Oramas, played by Bobby Cannavale.
Emily, played by Michelle Williams.
Cleo, played by Raven Goodwin.
Henry Styles, played by Paul Benjamin.
The Station Agent is a 2003 American comedy-drama film written and
directed by Tom McCarthy in his directorial debut.
It stars Peter Dinklage as a man who seeks solitude in an abandoned train station
in the Newfoundland section of Jefferson Township, New Jersey.
It also stars Patricia Clarkson, Michelle Williams,
Bobby Cannavale and John Slattery.
For his writing achievement, McCarthy won the BAFTA Award for Best Original Screenplay, the
Independent Spirit Award for Best First Screenplay and the Waldo Salt Screenwriting Award.
The film itself also won the John Cassavetes Award.
The film explores themes of friendship, new jersey, small person.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.